Zhu Yihai
Chaoyang
Aren't you my son?
You don't think 26 years in prison
wipes the slate clean between us, do you?
Chaoyang
Help! Help! Somebody help!
Bro Hai
What's wrong with you?
I really did become Zhu Yihai.
Who is it?
Who's there?
Wha- what's with the getup?
Hold on, let me put my pants on.
What the hell is this?
Bro Hai, weren't you going to change?
What did I say?
That head injury definitely left some damage.
Da Hai
Who clawed up your face like that?
What's going on?
You hiding someone in there?
Let me see.
You really are hiding someone!
No way.
Oh my God!
He turned this place into a total mess.
Goodness, what a mess.
I'll pick out your outfits from now on.
Wear this one on Monday.
Tuesday...
this one.
Wednesday...
this'll do.
Zhu Yihai's a lucky man.
Looks great.
I can tell you're distracted.
What's up?
Thinking about the Aimin Street deal?
Tell me.
What's your plan once you get that land?
That spot will be mine sooner or later.
Damn right, Bro.
Boss Long.
What are you two doing in my office?
Bro.
Have a seat.
Xie Fan.
Do you have a problem with the Zhu Yihai thing?
Yeah.
But he did save my life.
I gotta show my appreciation somehow.
Fine.
Bro, you do your thing.
No problem with you being generous.
But I'd like to see...
that holdout on Aimin Street,
sly old Director Ge,
the steel mill demolition...
just what is Zhu Yihai capable of?
Xie Fan.
Ambition is a good thing.
But everything has consequences.
Think before you act.
Sure.
Manager Xie.
We really should think before we act.
Like hell we should.
Abracadabra!
This reading...
This reading's not bad.
Director Ge, sorry to bother you.
This here is...
the factory's remaining budget for this quarter.
Alright.
Got it.
So how should I handle this account?
I-I-I... I mean...
Here's the thing.
Put this money...
all into this account.
The rest...
I'll handle.
Got it.
So this money...
I'll keep this part.
Alright.
I'll head back then, Director Ge.
Damn, he skims even from this.
Having such a great boss
is truly our blessing.
Hey buddy, you look new around here.
You're not from our factory, are you?
Don't even get me started.
I just got transferred back from out of town.
How did your factory end up like this?
Boss Hu said the factory's been doing badly.
They're cutting part of it.
At first it all sounded pretty good.
Once we were laid off,
we'd get some compensation money.
We could even start a small business.
And then?
Then out of nowhere,
some son of a bitch shows up.
Sweet-talked us, swindled us.
Not only did we never see the money,
the factory ended up in debt too.
Sorry about that.
Did I hurt you?
Something like that happened?
Who's this son of a bitch?
Boss Hu said
he's from the Giant Wood Group.
The number two.
But we're just regular folks.
Never actually seen the guy.
Boss Hu said,
if he ever finds out who it is,
he'll skin him alive.
The number two of Giant Wood Group...
What, you know him?
Yeah, I know him.
Isn't that Zhu Yihai from our factory?
Hey, Sis.
Bro, if you keep doing that,
I can't give you a massage.
You know what, forget the massage.
Come with me.
I'll take care of you.
Come on.
Bro, bro, don't do that.
Bro.
You just said
you know who the number two is, right?
I'm gonna build
a massive foot spa city
I've already got a name
What is it?
Monroe Foot Spa City
Why not Lili Foot Spa City?
You comparing yourself to Monroe?
Bro Hai
Why do you suddenly wanna do this?
What do you know?
This is the tertiary industry
You see?
Got it.
Alright.
If Bro Hai does it, he'll be number one.
I'm with you.
Dali
You got any dreams?
Sure I do.
My dream
is to buy a huge basket of red bean buns
I wouldn't even eat them
Just look at them.
Then what's the point?
Just for the joy of it!
Look at how pathetic you are.
What about you?
I'm kinda embarrassed to say.
My dream
If I make it big,
I'd definitely get a dual-cassette four-speaker stereo.
Oh, so ambitious.
What about you, Lili? Your dream?
Me?
What dream could I possibly have?
Just don't do anything stupid, that's enough.
Oh boy.
You bunch of bastards
Which one's Zhu Yihai?
And who are you?
What do you want with Bro Hai?
My little sis told me
if there's a score to settle, find Zhu Yihai.
Which one of you sons of bitches is it?
Hey, buddy
You're Zhu Yihai, right?
Me?
Pretty strong, huh?
Wait
Bro Hai
Don't fight.
Mind your own business!
Brother
My bro may have really wronged your sis
but I can't let you lay a hand on him.
Fine.
Good to know you're here.
Tonight at eight-thirty
bring your big guy,
Butterfly.
Let's settle this for real at the old station.
You know Night City's fighting rules, right?
No weapons in a Night City brawl.
Don't need you to tell me.
Good, as long as you know.
Hold on.
Small business here
Two bucks a head
counts the moment you step in.
Pay up if you've got money.
You think I owe you?
Take care now.
This old guy's even hooked up with someone's sister.
Bro Hai
Let's call for backup.
Just a few thugs from Dongxing Factory.
Did you see me take my hands out of my pockets?
We'll mess with them, no sweat.
What's wrong, Da Hai?
I figured I'd rub my temples
so I can remember what happened before
See if I can recall it
Bro, what do you need to remember?
That's the thing, I can't remember
That's why I'm trying to
How could I have hit on his sister?
Am I that kind of guy?
Yes